Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of Research, Vice President for Research Records, 1954-1975 RG.7.A
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
Ohio State University, Office of Research, Vice President for Research Records
1954-1975
RG.7.A
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
13.8 Cubic feet
In 1962, Ohio State University transferred research responsibilities from the Vice President for Instruction and Research and delegated them to the Vice President for Research. This position became the executive head of the Office of Research and President of the Research Foundation. The position ceased to exist on January 1, 1970. The Ohio State University, Office of Research, Vice President for Research Records contain grant proposals, correspondence, project reports, and other administrative records related to the Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963, the Ohio State University Research Foundation, and research activities in various colleges and departments on campus. The collection dates from 1954-1975.
(11) cartons, (1) 5" letter document box, (1) 2.5" letter document box
Ohio State University. Office of Research.
Arrangement of Materials
Materials are arranged in 5 series:
Series 1: General File
Series 2: Ohio State University Research Foundation
Series 3: Research Activity
Series 4: Federal Programs
Series 5: Grant Applications
Acquisitions Information
Accession Number UA.1971.0042: Office of Academic Affairs, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1972.0056: Graduate School, date unknown
Access to Materials
Materials in this collection are available for patron research, but may be used only in the University Archives Reading Room.
Historical Note
In 1962, Ohio State University transferred research responsibilities from the Vice President for Instruction and Research and delegated them to the Vice President for Research. This position became the executive head of the Office of Research, and was filled by the chairman of the Department of Chemistry, Alfred B. Garrett. Garrett also filled the role of Research Foundation President. The position ceased to exist on January 1, 1970, when Dr. Garrett resigned to return to teaching chemistry. Responsibilities for research were then combined with the Office of Academic Affairs, and a Vice President for Research and Sponsored Programs was appointed.
Scope and Contents
Ohio State University, Office of Research, Vice President for Research Records contain grant proposals, correspondence, project reports, and other administrative records related to the Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963 and other federal programs, the Ohio State University Research Foundation, and research activities in various colleges and departments on campus. The collection dates from 1954-1975.
Related Materials
RG 53.A
Ohio State University, Office of Academic Affairs, Office of Research, Senior Vice President for Research Records
Ohio State University Archives Subject File
Office of Vice President for Research
Ohio State University--Administration.; Ohio State University--History.; Ohio State University--Research.; Ohio State University. Office of Research.; Ohio State University. Research Foundation.; United States. Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963.; Grant proposals; Research--Management--20th century; State universities and colleges--Ohio--Columbus--Administration--20th century; State universities and colleges--Research--Ohio--Columbus--20th century
- Processed, 1954-1975; 13.8 Cubic feet; (11) cartons, (1) 5" letter document box, (1) 2.5" letter document box
  - General File, 1959-1975; Series 1
    - Academic Image Booklet, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Accelerator (Large), 1965-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Administrative Services Center (ASC), 1964-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Agricultural Biochemistry, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Antenna Laboratory (2 folders), 1965-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Argonne Universities Association (4 folders), 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Associated Midwest Universities (AMU) (2 folders), 1965-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Association of American Universities, 1965-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Atmospheric Sciences, 1963-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1963-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Barken -- Aesthetics, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Biological Engineering Research, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Biological Sciences, 1964-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Biological Survey, 1962-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Biomedical Engineering Council, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (NIH), 1967-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Biomedical Support Grants (Colleges): Reports, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Biometeorology, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Biophysics, 1964-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Board of Regents: Science Advisory Committee, 1964-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Board of Regents: Slide Presentation, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Botany Department, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Budget Materials, 1963-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Bureau of Business Research, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Byrd Memorial, 1963-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Cady, Henry L.: Proposal, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - California Alumni, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - Capital Improvement Needs, 1967-1973 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0001)
    - "Cat" Problem, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Catalysis Institute, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - CCH Specials Log, 1965-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Center for Adolescents, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Center for Advanced Studies, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Center for Experimental Research in The Arts (2 folders), 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Centers of Excellence (2 folders), 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Columbus, Ohio), 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Chemistry, Department of, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Children's Hospital -- Board of Trustees (2 folders), 1962-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Children's Hospital -- Minutes of the Board of Trustees and other committees, 1964-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Computer Center: Advisory Committee, 1965-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Computer Center: Data Processing System (DPS), 1963-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Computer Center: General (4 folders), 1963-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Computer Center: Interim Plans for, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Computer Center: Proposals for, 1964-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Computer Center: Purchase of Computers, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0002)
    - Computer System 6500: Proposal, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Cooperative Career Development, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Corson Experimental Area in Psychiatric Institute, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Cost Sharing Agreement: Public Health Service, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Council on Research: New Members - Programs, 1963, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Creativity: Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Cuta, Frank (Dr.): Correspondence, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Data Processing Centralization: Feasibility Analysis, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Data Processing System, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Departmental Development Program, 1970 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Development Fund, 1963-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Earner's Feedback: Proposal, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Earth Sciences (ESCP), 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - East-West Center (Honolulu, Hawaii), 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Ecological Research and Surveys Bill (Natural Resources), 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Education, College of, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Educational Television Facilities, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Electronics Laboratory, 1965-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Entomology, Department of, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Environmental Health: Department of Preventive Medicine, Department of Physiology, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Experienced Teacher Fellowship Program, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Faculty Council, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Federal Aid to Research, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Fellowships: NDEA, NSF, NASA, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Firestone Tire and Rubber Company: R.L. Bebb (Akron, Ohio), 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Food Protein Center: Proposal for -- Correspondence, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Ford Foundation, (New York), 1962 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Foundations, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Gifts, Grants and Contracts, Revisions, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Grant-in-Aid Allocation Reports (3 folders), 1959-1970 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Guidelines for Sponsored Research, 1971 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Hamilton, Nancy: Questionnaire in Science, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Health Sciences Advancement Award (3 folders), 1965-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Health Sciences Library, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - High Energy Physics: AEC Grant, 1965-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - High Energy Physics: Romanowski, T.A. (Dr.), 1963-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Highway Research and Development Center, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - History of Science: Project, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Housing Urban Development (HUD), 1966, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0003)
    - Human Subjects (2 folders), 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Humanities and Arts, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Hutchison, Clyde A. (Dr.): Correspondence, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Hydrocarbon Samples: Chemistry Department, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Industrial Arts Curriculum Project (I.A.C.P. Advisory Committee), 1965, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Industrial Research Report, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Information Science, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Institute for Perinatal Studies, 1959-1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Institute for Research in Vision, 1963-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Institute of Natural Resources (2 folders), 1962-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Institute of Nutrition and Food Technology (2 folders), 1962-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Institute of Polar Studies (2 folders), 1964-1970 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Institutes, Notes on, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Integrated Research Budget, 1964-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - International Biological Program, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - International Programs, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Journalism, School of, 1965-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Keller, Martin (Dr.), 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Khmelnitskiy, L. I. (Dr.): Russian Scholar, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Kim, Y. S. (Professor of Physics): Computer, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Kouyoumjian, Robert G. (Professor): Case, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Kraus, John Daniel (Dr.) Professor of Electrical Engineering: Nominees for Regents Professor, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Laboratory Animals: Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on, 1964, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Laboratory Animals: Expenses, 1960-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Laboratory Animals: General (4 folders), 1959-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Laboratory Animals: Inspection Reports (2 folders), 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0004)
    - Laboratory Animals: National Institute of Health, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Laboratory Animals: Physical Facilities, 1963-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Laboratory Animals: Physical Facilities, Blueprints, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Laboratory Animals: Physical Facilities, Psychology, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Laboratory Animals: Physical Facilities, Research Center, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Laboratory Animals: Physical Facilities, Site Visit, 1965, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Laboratory Animals Center: Proposal, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Lake Erie Laboratory, 1966, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Laser Agreement: College of Medicine and Eastman Kodak, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Latin American Center, undated (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Library: General (2 folders), 1965-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Library: Library Science, The Graduate School, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Library: Library Stacks Construction, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Library: Medical, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Library: Ohio College Library Center, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Literature Retrieval, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Litvinov, V. P. (Dr.): (Chemistry in Russia), 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Long-Term Planning, 1969-1975 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Lunar Space Institute, 1967-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
      General note
      (See Also: Universities Research Association)
    - Man: A Course of Study (College of Education)- Proposal, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - McKitrick Property: Don Scott Field, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - McMasters, Robert (Dr.) Welding Engineering, OSU: Nominee for Scott Award, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Medical and Renaissance Studies, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Memos (Received), 1970 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Mershon Center for Education: Budget, 1963-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Mershon Committee on Education in National Security: Minutes and Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Meyer, Donald E., Psychology Department OSU, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Microbiology, Department of, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Midwestern Universities Research Association (MURA) (2 folders), 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - Miller-Daddario Bill, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) (3 folders), 1964-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - National Institutes of Health: Construction, 1965-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - National Institutes of Health: Correspondence, Restriction on International Travel, 1968; Grant Policies and Procedures, 1964-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - National Medal of Science Award, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0005)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1965-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF): Centers of Excellence - Preliminary Proposal, 1965-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF): Information on Grants for Undergraduate Laboratory Equipment, 1963, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF): Ohio State University Research Foundation: Correspondence; Active RF Projects CJI, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Natural Resources, School of: Correspondence, Proposals, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Neotoma Ecological and Bioenvironmental Laboratory: Lease (Hocking County), 1964-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Nuclear Reactor (2 folders), 1964-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Nuclear Reactor: Operation; Advisory Committee, 1965-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Nuclear Research and Development, 1965-1966, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Numerical Computation Laboratory: General, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Oceanography: Gravity Data Center, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Ohio Biological Survey, 1966-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Ohio Historical Society: Building, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Ohio River Division Laboratory (ORDL), 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Ohio State Historical Society: Natural History Collection - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Ohio State Historical Society: Natural History Collection - Reports (2 folders), 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Ohio Valley Assembly, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Oral History Center for Latin America, 1966-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Oral History Program for Latin America: Research Papers, 1967-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Oxley Hall: Problem, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Panel Members: Colleges, National Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Penta County Technical Institute, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Pharmacy, College of, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Photography, Department of, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Physical Education, Department of, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Physics and Astronomy Building, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Physics Building: New Addition, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Plant Pathology, Department of, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Population Studies: Ad Hoc Committee, 1962-1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Post Doctoral: Reports, Correspondence, Exhibits, 1964-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - President's Report (Extended Outline), 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Proposals (Model copy), 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Psychology, Department of, 1963-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Radiation Safety Committee, 1962-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0006)
    - Radiation Safety Committee, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Radio Observatory, 1965-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Regents Material: State Appropriations vs. Federal Grants, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Regents Professors, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Repertory Theatre, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research, Office of, 1968-1970 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research Administrations: Ohio Universities, 1967-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research vs. Instruction, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research Center (OSU): Proposal for, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research Center (OSU), 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research Committee: Report for Faculty Council, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research Council, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research Foundation: Project Reports, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research Grants: Analysis by Department, 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Research Officers (Colleges, OSU), 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Richland County Technical Institute (2 folders), 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Safe Practices, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Salmon, Raphael J., 1964-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - "Scholars Bill": House Bill #315-302, 1963-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Science Development Program, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Social Science Research Center, Plans for: By Professor Lawrence Krader, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Space Assignment (Research), 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Space Needs, 1964-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Speaker's Rule, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Stadium: Bay under 2d, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - State Technical Services Act (3 folders), 1965-1970 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Statistics Department, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Stone Laboratory, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Summer Fellowships: (Accepted), 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Summer Fellowships: Development Fund (Faculty), 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Summer Fellowships: (Rejected), 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0007)
    - Systems Engineering Building, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Technical Services Act, 1966-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Television Link Between OSU Campus and Wright-Patterson AFB, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Themis Project, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Traffic Study, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Transportation Research Center, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Universities Research Association, 1967-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - University College, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - University Research Administrators, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Urban Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Urban Corps: College Work-Study Program, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Van de Graaff Laboratory, 1964-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Veterinary Medicine, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Veterinary Medicine, College of: Grant, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Veterinary Medicine, College of: Large Animal Isolation Ward, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Veterinary Medicine, College of: Veterinary Practice (Marysville, Ohio), 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Vocational Education: National Center, 1964, 1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - War Research Building, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Water Related Programs: Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1967-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Water Resources: Advisory Committee -- Minutes, 1965-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Water Resources: Correspondence (2 folders), 1963-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Weed, Herman R.: Correspondence, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - West Campus Planning, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
  - Ohio State University Research Foundation, 1954-1969; Series 2
    - Board of Directors (4 folders), 1955-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Board of Directors: Annual Meeting, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Budget, 1964-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Charter and Code of Regulations, 1954, 1956, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Consultants, 1956, 1963, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Contingency Funds, 1962-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1963-1965, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Cost Sharing, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Delinquenty Reports on Grants and Contracts, 1964-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Executive Committee, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0008)
    - Executive Committee (2 folders), 1966-1969 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Financial Statements, 1964-1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Management Study: Report, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - National Science Foundation: Ceiling, 1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - New Employee Contract, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology, Department of, 1964, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Office Expansion: Plans, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - "Organization, Objectives, Policies, and Procedures", 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Overhead Funds, 1965-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Projects, Active, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Project 1239: Obstetrics and Gynecology Department, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Rental Space, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Reserve Funds: Administration of, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Review Committee, 1962 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Security Manual for Classified Material, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Stephenson, Robert C. (Executive Director of American Geological Institute), 1962-1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Storage Room, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Systems Management Study, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Travel: Per Diem, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - University Research Parks, undated (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Woolperty Oram (Dr.): Retirement, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
  - Research Activity, 1960-1969; Series 3
    Sub-Group
    - Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering Department of, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology, Department of, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Agricultural Engineering, Department of, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Agriculture, College of, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Agronomy, Department of, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Arts and Sciences, College of, 1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Astronomy, Department of, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Botany and Plant Pathology, Department of, undated (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Bureau of Business Research, 1963 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Chemistry, Department of, 1965 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Commerce and Administration, College of, 1963-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Defense Management Center, 1962-1964 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Dentistry, College of, 1964, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Education, College of, 1964-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Engineering Experiment Station, 1965-1968 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - English, Department of, 1963, 1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Food Technology, Institute of, 1961-1966 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)
    - Geodetic Sciences, Department of, 1963-1967 (Box UA.RG.7.A.0009)